bingo.com 2001-11-01

# Bingo.com - Free online bingo. Bingo chat, play bingo games, video poker, free sweepstakes.

** PRIVACY POLICY**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Bingo.com realizes that privacy on the Internet is a great concern to many people. Bingo.com has created this privacy policy to clarify its collection and use of personal information. Please note that this site contains links to other sites and Bingo.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any website not owned or operated by Bingo.com. The following policy describes and discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of Bingo.com. 

**1\. Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
In general, Bingo.com gathers personal information about its users when they voluntarily register to use our services, enter certain contests or sweepstakes and when Bingo.com aggregates information gathered by tracking the usage of certain features available on the Website. PLEASE NOTE: THE PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US IS THE RESULT OF A COMPLETELY VOLUNTARY ACTION IN REGISTERING TO PLAY OUR GAMES OR USE OUR SITE. THE SPECIFIC DEMOGRAPHIC DATA AND TRACKING INFORMATION WE COLLECT WILL BE SHARED WITH OUR ADVERTISERS, SPONSORS AND BUSINESS ASSOCIATES. THEREFORE, YOUR REGISTRATION AND USE OF OUR WEBSITE CONSTITUTES YOUR CONSENT TO OUR COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. Our collection and use of personal information will enable us to tailor our content to your needs and to help our advertisers, sponsors and business associates better understand the demographics of our audience, which is essential to providing Bingo.com as a free service to you as the consumer. 

**2\. Registration Process**  
Our site's registration form requires new users to provide a "user name" (their "handle" or moniker on our system) and contact information in the form of their e-mail address. We also require new users to enter general demographic information (such as their U.S. zip code, age range, gender, and country). During the registration process, the user may have the option to receive our promotional correspondence and those of selected companies we do business with. 

**3\. Website Tracking Data**  
We use "cookies" (see definition below) and other methods to monitor your use of our Website. This traffic data is collected and used by our company in many ways, including, among others, to determine your specific use of our Website, to track your selection and or purchase of products, to determine high-traffic areas of our site, to locate areas of improvement to our service, to judge how well certain content areas are received, and to select additional content areas for our service, etc...We also collect information on the "stickiness" of certain Web pages and share this date with third parties. PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IS USED IN THIS TRACKING PROCEDURE AND PERSONAL INFORMATION IS SHARED WITH THIRD PARTIES AS ALREADY STATED HEREIN. 

**4\. "Cookies"**  
A cookie is a small data file that certain Websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. They are designed to enhance your browsing experience on the site. A cookie file can contain information such as screen names and passwords, demographic information and other tracking data. The only personal information a cookie contains is the information you supply yourself. Our cookies cannot read any information, personal or otherwise, from your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites. Bingo.com uses cookies to track user traffic patterns when you register as a user, and when you click on an advertisement. 

**5\. Feedback**  
Our users have the option to provide us with feedback and also to report "bugs" (defects) in our games. This feedback is read and reviewed by Bingo.com employees and forwarded to the appropriate department in our company (i.e., engineering, marketing, etc.). Both the feedback and "bug" reporting forms ask for the user's screen name and an e-mail address and may ask what browser and version of browser the user has on their computer. The information and email address may be used in case we need further information about a reported "bug" or for other feedback-related purposes, and could therefore be distributed to third parties. 

Our feedback section is designed to be used in a number of ways. Users can report on abusive players (which are identified by their screen name) a request features or games to our service, pass along compliments or gripes, and enter various other comments. 

"Bug" reports are entered by our users and contain information on the following: problems with our registration process, problems with a specific game, browser issues and compatibility problems, and other miscellaneous problems. 

Feedback and "bug" reports, and the data therein, are primarily gathered for our internal use, but may be distributed to third parties. 

**6\. Member Surveys**  
We may occasionally run marketing-driven surveys on our site. These surveys are used to fully understand our audience, to provide better service, as a factor in determining new features and games to add to our service and to collect more specific aggregate demographic information. These surveys are always optional to the user. 

Data collected from member surveys are used by our marketing department and could be shared with our advertisers and sponsors. 

**7\. Prizes And Verification Information**  
Some of Bingo.com's games reward successful players with prizes that can take the form of cash or other miscellaneous prizes. These prizes are only eligible to certain residents of the United States and Canada (excluding Quebec) that are 18 years of age or more. 

Cash prizes require the collection of specific personal individual information for income tax purposes. This specific information includes: full legal name, complete address (city, state, country and zip/postal code), a social security number (social insurance number in Canada) and date of birth. All information must be completed in full as described in our Affidavit of Eligibility and must be accurate in order to receive a prize. If this information is not collected and verified, the prize will not be awarded. 

Bingo.com also reserves the right to use the collected personal information in advertising, promotional and/or marketing materials as described in our Rules section and the Liability and Publicity release on our Web-based prize claim form. 

**8\. Miscellaneous Information Collected and Used**  
In addition to the above-listed data that we collect or track, we also display some non-personally identifiable data. These items consist of player rating information (your skill level and ranking on a particular game), any prize winnings, and player games statistics (number of games played, wins and losses, etc.) In the cases stated on the previous line, only a player's screen name (their chosen "handle") will be displayed, and no personally-identifiable information will be shown, unless the screen name the user has chosen is somehow personally identifiable. 

**9\. Use Of Public Chat Rooms**  
As part of our service, Bingo.com provides areas where players can chat with other users. Users in these chat rooms are identified solely by their user-created screen names on our service. Please remember, however, that any information you disclose within this context/forum becomes public knowledge. You should exercise caution before disclosing any information to other users in a public chat room, and Bingo.com is not responsible for any information you choose to disclose to other users. 

**10\. Why We Collect And Distribute Personal Information**  
Because Bingo.com derives its revenue primarily from advertisers, sponsors and business associates, providing demographic data from registration, surveys and the like is crucial to our business strategy and to keeping our service free for you. We provide this data to our advertisers, sponsors and business associates so that they can better understand you and create better offers for you. In addition, this data may be used internally by us to find ways to improve our service and provide a better user experience for you. 

**11\. Business Associates**  
Our business associates are companies with whom Bingo.com has established relationships with to provide communications services, games, personalized marketing, prizes, and other products and services to Bingo.com. 

**12\. How To Correct Or Update Information**  
You have the ability to correct or update information we collect about you when you register for the Bingo.com service by using our online 'Edit Profile' form located at http://bingo.com/user_edit.php You may change this information at any time and as often as necessary. If you ever experience problems with our service or have any questions about it, please contact us at any time at bingo.com. 

**13\. Security**  
Bingo.com has implemented security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. Once your information is in our possession we take every precaution to protect it against unauthorized access. 

**14\. Contacting Bingo.com**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Website, you can contact us at: 

By Mail: 

Bingo.com  
4223 Glencoe Avenue, Suite C200   
Marina Del Rey, CA USA 90292   

By Phone: 

Tel. 310-301-4171  
Fax 310-301-4172  

Investor Relations: 

Toll Free 1-877-755-1860 

Bingo.com works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>.
